{
  "questions": {
    "FILL": [
      {
        "0": "{val}",
        "1": "{0} + {val}",
        "answer": "{1}-{0}",
        "question": "{0} + ____ = {1}"
      },
      {
        "0": "{val}",
        "1": "{0} + {val}",
        "answer": "{1}-{0}",
        "question": "{1} - ____ = {0}"
      },
      {
        "0": "{val}",
        "1": "{0} + {val}",
        "answer": "{1}-{0}",
        "question": "____ + {0} = {1}"
      },
      {
        "0": "{val}",
        "1": "{val}",
        "answer": "{1}+{0}",
        "question": "____ - {1} = {0}"
      },
      {
        "0": "{val}",
        "1": "{val}",
        "2": "{0} + {1} + {val}",
        "answer": "{2}-{0}-{1}",
        "question": "{2} - ____ = {0} + {1}"
      },
      {
        "0": "{val}",
        "1": "{val}",
        "2": "{val}",
        "answer": "{1}+{0}+{2}",
        "question": "____ - {0} - {1} = {2}"
      },
      {
        "0": "{val}",
        "1": "{0}+{val}",
        "2": "{0}+{val}",
        "answer": "{1}+{2}-{0}",
        "question": "____ + {0} = {1} + {2}"
      },
      {
        "0": "{val}",
        "1": "{val}",
        "2": "{0}+{1}+{val}",
        "answer": "{2}-{0}-{1}",
        "question": "____ + {0} + {1} = {2}"
      },
      {
        "0": "{val}",
        "1": "{0}+{val}",
        "2": "{0}+{val}",
        "answer": "{1}+{2}-{0}",
        "question": "{1} + {2} - ___ = {0}"
      },
      {
        "0": "{val}",
        "1": "{val}",
        "2": "{0}+{1}+{val}",
        "answer": "{2}-{0}-{1}",
        "question": "{2} - ___ = {0} + {1}"
      },
      {
        "0": "{val}",
        "1": "{val}",
        "2": "{0}+{1}+{val}",
        "answer": "{2}-{0}-{1}",
        "question": "{0} + {1} + ___ = {2}"
      },
      {
        "0": "{val}",
        "1": "{0}+{val}",
        "2": "{0}+{val}",
        "answer": "{1}+{2}-{0}",
        "question": "{0} + ___ = {1} + {2}"
      }
    ],
    "WORD": [
      {
        "0": {
          "val": "{val}/100",
          "min": 1001,
          "max": 6999
        },
        "answer": "70-{0}",
        "question": "Arlo has a £50 and a £20 note. Ken has £{0}. How much more money does Arlo have than Ken?"
      },
      {
        "0": {
          "val": "{val}",
          "min": 10,
          "max": 24
        },
        "answer": "72.45-({0}*3)",
        "question": "Elliot earns £{0} every time he mows the lawn. He mows the lawn three times. How much more does he need to save to buy a skateboard that costs £72.45?"
      }
    ],
    "MONEY": [
      {
        "0": "{val}",
        "1": "{val}",
        "answer": "{0}+{1}",
        "question": "Ben has {0}p and Sonia has {1}p. How much money do they have together?",
        "active": "N"
      },
      {
        "0": "{val}",
        "1": "{val}",
        "answer": "{0}+{1}",
        "question": "Angela buys a pencil for {0}p and a notebook for {1}p at a store. How much did she spent?",
        "active": "N"
      },
      {
        "0": "{val}",
        "1": "{val}",
        "answer": "{0}+{1}",
        "question": "Grace has {0}p. Her brother has {1}p. How much do they have together?",
        "active": "N"
      },
      {
        "0": "{val}",
        "answer": "{0}*2",
        "question": "Rachel wants to buy a bracelet for herself and for her friend. Each bracelet costs {0}p. How much money will Rachel need?",
        "active": "N"
      },

      {
        "0": {
          "val": "{val}",
          "list": [20, 50]
        },
        "1": {
          "val": "{val}",
          "list": [1, 2, 5, 10]
        },
        "2": "{val}",
        "answer": "({0}+(3*{1}))+({2}*10)",
        "question": "Jason has a {0}p coin and three {1}p coins, then he found {2} 10p coins. How much _____p does Jason have now?"
      },

      {
        "0": {
          "val": "{val}",
          "min": 1,
          "max": 9
        },
        "1": {
          "val": "{val}",
          "list": [10, 20, 50]
        },
        "2": {
          "val": "{val}",
          "min": 1,
          "max": 9
        },
        "3": {
          "val": "{val}",
          "list": [1, 2, 5]
        },
        "4": {
          "val": "{val}",
          "min": 1,
          "max": 9
        },
        "5": {
          "val": "{val}",
          "list": [10, 20, 50]
        },
        "6": {
          "val": "{val}",
          "min": 1,
          "max": 9
        },
        "7": {
          "val": "{val}",
          "list": [1, 2, 5]
        },
        "8": {
          "val": "{val}",
          "min": 1,
          "max": 90
        },
        "answer": "(({0}*{1})+({2}*{3})+({4}*{5})+({6}*{7})+{8})/100",
        "question": "Ava has a lemonade stand. She earned {0} {1}p coins and {2} {3}p coins in the morning. In the afternoon she earned {4} {5}p coins and {6} {7}p coins. In the evening she earned {8}p. How much £ ____ did she make all together?"
      },
      {
        "0": {
          "val": "{val}",
          "min": 3,
          "max": 9
        },
        "1": {
          "val": "{val}",
          "list": [20, 50]
        },
        "2": {
          "val": "{val}",
          "min": 3,
          "max": 9
        },
        "3": {
          "val": "{val}",
          "list": [1, 2, 5, 10]
        },
        "answer": "({0}*{1})+({2}*{3})-55",
        "question": "Evan had {0} {1}p coins and {2} {3}p coins, then he bought a toy car for 55p. How much money did he have left after the purchase?"
      },
      {
        "0": {
          "val": "{val}",
          "min": 10,
          "max": 50
        },
        "1": "({val}+{0}*5)/100",
        "answer": "(({1}*100-{0}*5)*100)/10000",
        "question": "The library charges {0}p each day a book is late. Koki had one book that was 5 days late. If she had £{1} before paying this fee, how much does she have after the fee is paid in Pounds?"
      },
      {
        "0": {
          "val": "{val}/100",
          "min": 1001,
          "max": 9999
        },
        "1": {
          "val": "({val}/100)+{0}",
          "min": 1001,
          "max": 9999
        },
        "answer": "{1}-{0}",
        "question": "Jimmy has £{0}. He wants to buy a video game that costs £{1}. How much more money does he need?"
      },
      {
        "0": {
          "val": "{val}/100",
          "min": 1001,
          "max": 9999
        },
        "1": {
          "val": "({val}/100)+{0}",
          "min": 1001,
          "max": 9999
        },
        "answer": "{1}-{0}",
        "question": "Chris has £{0} and Martin has £{1}. How much more money  does Martin have than Chris?"
      },
      {
        "0": {
          "val": "{val}/100",
          "min": 1001,
          "max": 9999
        },
        "1": {
          "val": "({val}/100)+{0}",
          "min": 1001,
          "max": 9999
        },
        "answer": "{1}-{0}",
        "question": "Jimmy has £{0}. She wants to buy a new e-reader tablet. It costs £{1}. How much more money does she need to save?"
      },
      {
        "0": {
          "val": "{val}/100",
          "min": 1001,
          "max": 6999
        },
        "answer": "70-{0}",
        "question": "Arlo has a £50 and a £20 note. Ken has £{0}. How much more money does Arlo have than Ken?"
      },
      {
        "0": {
          "val": "{val}",
          "min": 10,
          "max": 24
        },
        "answer": "72.45-({0}*3)",
        "question": "Elliot earns £{0} every time he mows the lawn. He mows the lawn three times. How much more does he need to save to buy a skateboard that costs £72.45?"
      },
      {
        "0": {
          "val": "{val}/100",
          "min": 10000,
          "max": 99999
        },
        "1": {
          "val": "{0}+({val}/100)",
          "min": 10000,
          "max": 50000
        },
        "answer": "{1}-{0}",
        "question": "Sara is looking at computers. The first computer costs £{1}. The second costs £{0}. How much more is the first computer?"
      },
      {
        "0": {
          "val": "{val}/100",
          "min": 10000,
          "max": 99999
        },
        "1": {
          "val": "{0}+({val}/100)",
          "min": 10000,
          "max": 50000
        },
        "answer": "{1}-{0}",
        "question": "Sara wants the computer that costs £{1}. She currently has £{0} saved. How much more money does she need to buy it?"
      },
      {
        "0": {
          "val": "{val}/100",
          "min": 10000,
          "max": 99999
        },
        "1": {
          "val": "{0}+({val}/100)",
          "min": 1000,
          "max": 9900
        },
        "answer": "{1}-{0}",
        "question": "Maria had £{1} before buying concert tickets. If the tickets were £{0}, how much money does she have after the purchase?"
      },
      {
        "0": {
          "val": "{val}/100",
          "min": 10000,
          "max": 49999
        },
        "1": {
          "val": "{val}/100",
          "min": 10000,
          "max": 49999
        },
        "2": {
          "val": "{0}+{1}+({val}/100)",
          "min": 1000,
          "max": 9900
        },
        "answer": "{2}-{0}-{1}",
        "question": "Isaac and Josh want to buy an £{2} fishing boat together. Isaac has £{0} saved. Josh has £{1} saved. How much more money do they need before they can buy the boat?"
      }
    ],
    "CONVERSIONS": [
      {
        "0": "{val}",
        "answer": "1000*{0}",
        "question": "How many milliliter (ml) in {0} liter (l)?",
        "active": "Y"
      },
      {
        "0": "{val}",
        "answer": "1000*{0}",
        "question": "How many milligrams (mg) in {0} grams (g)?",
        "active": "Y"
      },
      {
        "0": "{val}",
        "answer": "1000*{0}",
        "question": "How may grams (g) in {0} Kilogram (KG)?",
        "active": "Y"
      },
      {
        "0": "{val}",
        "answer": "100*{0}",
        "question": "How many centimeters (cm) in {0} Meters (m)?",
        "active": "Y"
      },
      {
        "0": "{val}",
        "answer": "1000*{0}",
        "question": "How many meters (m) in {0} Kilometer (KM)?",
        "active": "Y"
      },
      {
        "0": "{val}",
        "answer": "12*{0}",
        "question": "How many months in {0} year?",
        "active": "Y"
      },
      {
        "0": "{val}",
        "answer": "52*{0}",
        "question": "How many weeks in {0} year?",
        "active": "Y"
      },
      {
        "0": "1",
        "answer": "365",
        "question": "How many days in a year?",
        "active": "Y"
      },
      {
        "0": "{val}",
        "answer": "2*{0}",
        "question": "How many weeks in {0} fortnight?",
        "active": "Y"
      },
      {
        "0": "{val}",
        "answer": "7*{0}",
        "question": "How many days in {0} week(s)?",
        "active": "Y"
      },
      {
        "0": "{val}",
        "answer": "24*{0}",
        "question": "How many hours in {0} days?",
        "active": "Y"
      },
      {
        "0": "{val}",
        "answer": "60*{0}",
        "question": "How many minutes in {0} hours?",
        "active": "Y"
      },
      {
        "0": "{val}",
        "answer": "60*{0}",
        "question": "How many seconds in {0} minutes?",
        "active": "Y"
      },
      {
        "0": {
          "val": "{val}",
          "min": 1,
          "max": 12
        },
        "answer": "({0}==4 or {0} == 6 or {0} == 9 or {0} == 11)?30:(({0}==2)?28:31)",
        "question": "How many days in the month {0}?",
        "active": "Y"
      }
    ]
  }
}